Some lines you just have to cross.
Little Woods is a drama, thriller film directed by Nia DaCosta.
For years, Ollie has illicitly helped the struggling residents of her North
Dakota oil boomtown access Canadian health care and medication.
When the authorities catch on, she plans to abandon her crusade, only to be
dragged in even deeper after a desperate plea for help from her sister.
Oleander 'Ollie' Hale, played by Tessa Thompson.
Deborah Hale, played by Lily James.
Bill, played by Luke Kirby.
Ian, played by James Badge Dale.
Carter, played by Lance Reddick.
Jenny, played by Elizabeth Maxwell.
Little Woods is a 2018 crime drama film, written and directed by
Nia DaCosta in her feature directorial debut.
The film stars Tessa Thompson, Lily James, Luke Kirby,
James Badge Dale and Lance Reddick.
Little Woods had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on 21 April 2018, and was released on 19 April
2019 in the United States by Neon and on 16 May 2019 in Australia by Limelight Distribution.
In the United Kingdom, it was released both digitally and on DVD as
Crossing the Line on 29 April 2019 by Signature Entertainment.
The film explores themes of canada, health care, north
dakota, prescription medication, abortion.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.